Welcome to DealingTree.com!
Use the menu near the beginning of the page
to navigate the site.
To begin, select Join.
Answer all of the prompts
completely and accurately
Then click Sign up!
Then, to start saving, check
out the deals on the home page
For fastest access to relevant deals
allow the site to determine
your location if prompted.
You can also choose a location
using the drop-down selection.
Click a title for details about a deal
including the provider, location,
description, and even reviews.
Back on the home screen, you can
instantly purchase a deal by dragging
it to the Your Deals area.
If your browser does not
support drag-and-drop
simply click a Buy button
to purchase a deal instantly.
Thank you for saving with us!